question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In the movie Shrek film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Leonardo da Vinci's Mona Lisa does not have eyebrows.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The S in Harry S. Truman stands for Samuel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "There was a satirical candidate named Deez Nuts running in the 2016 US presidential elections.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Berenstein Bears is the correct spelling of the educational children's book series name.",
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                              "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Gadgets", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The communication protocol NFC stands for Near-Field Control.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "An average human can go two weeks without water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
